(Penny:)I'm the one that introduced him to her.
I've gotta say something.
(Penny:)Wow.
(Penny:)- You're engaged to my friend.
- Hey, Bernadette doesn't mind...
(Howard:)...where I get my motor running,
as long as I park in the right garage.
(Penny:)I can't believe you're engaged
to my friend.
(Penny:)Oh, here she comes.
(Howard:)Smart. Whisper,
so the deaf chick can't hear you.
(Sheldon:)- Hi.
- Oh, hey. Hi. Nice to see you.
(Penny:)Um, can we talk to you about Raj?
She says, "Sure, what about him?"
(Penny:)Okay. Um, gosh, how do I start?
(Penny:)Um, see, Raj is kind of naive.
(Penny:)He hasn't dated
a whole lot of women.
(Penny:)And I'm concerned that,
without meaning to...
(Penny:)...you might be taking advantage
of him.
(Penny:)By letting him buy you
a bunch of expensive things.